姑娘们在干啥呢
Hey, girls. Whatcha you doing?
我们在列清单呢
Oh we're making a list of all the fun things
统计一下上大学前想做的有意思的事
we want to do together before we go to college.
类似遗愿清单
Kind of like a bucket list
只不过我们不是要挂了  而是要毕业了
except instead of dying, we're graduating.
这样啊  那你们弄的咋样了
Oh okay. Well, what do you have so far?
才写完清单二字
The word "List".
还是我想出来的
I came up with that.
我能给你们好的建议
I have the perfect idea for you girls.
来次热气球之旅怎么样
How about you take a ride in a hot-air balloon?
听上去不错啊
Ooh, that sounds good.
是吧
Yup.
但是我恐高
Then again, I am afraid of heights.
而且我不太喜欢气球
And I'm not crazy about balloons.
那去派克峰顶看日出呢
Okay, how about watching the sunrise from the top of Pike's Peak.
我一直想去来着
Oh, I've always wanted to do that.
那就意味着咱们得早起
Of course we'd have to get up pretty early.
我敢打赌上面一定很冷
And I bet it's cold up there.
零比二  老妈
0 for 2, ma.
那你们怎么不自个儿想呢
Okay, why don't you two come up with something?
自驾游
Road trip.
好主意啊
That's sounds like fun.
完事
Done.
-休息一下  -休息一下
- Take a break? - Take a break.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late and dad jokes.
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe?
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： Tracy  Crazy王
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud.
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof.
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I survived.
■
校订： Enpistu
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice.
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy.
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
可是我知道你会有美好将来
But I know your future's bright.
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
不要怀疑
There's no maybe.
一切终会如你所愿
Everything turns out all right.
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down.
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back around.
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be.
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby.
查莉成长日记  第四季第十三集
Good Luck Charlie  S04E13  Weekend in Vegas
邻居们好啊
Hey, neighbors.
因为啥事让你们亲自登门拜访
To what do we owe the honor?
我们要宣布一个激动人心的消息
We came over because we have some exciting news.
是的  我们要结婚了
Yeah, we're getting married.
你们不是才刚开始约会吗
Didn't you two just start dating?
到了我们这个年纪  要惜时如金啊
At our age, you don't waste time.
哇  那恭喜你们了  祝你俩长年快乐
Wow, well, congratulations and, you know, many happy years.
等会
Yeah, hold on.
-嘿  那啥  RJ  -PJ
- Hey, listen, R.J. - P.J.
随便了  管你叫啥
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
我想让你做我的伴郎
I want you to be my best man.
我  为啥呀
Me? Why me?
因为你是我最亲密的朋友
Well, because you're my closest friend...
还健在的人中
You know, who's living.
嗯  你也是我的
Yeah, as you are mine...
如果我别的朋友都惨遭不测的话
Should something terrible happen to all my friends.
鲍伯  我们希望你能为我们主持仪式
And, Bob, we'd love it if you would perform the ceremony.
我
Me?
你可以上网弄个资质
You can be certified online.
我都查过了
I looked into it.
没错
Yeah...
我们想既然要在你家举行婚礼
We figured you'd be the right
那你应该是最好的人选
choice since we're having the wedding in your house.
啥玩意
Excuse me?
我们想弄个旅行婚礼
We wanted to have a destination wedding.
是的  所以我们觉得“街对面”
Yeah, so we thought "Across the street"...
是很好的目的地啊
Is the perfect destination.
你觉得咋样
So what do you say?
-呃  那啥  -谢了
- Eh, well... - Thanks.
这对我们意义重大
That means an awful lot to us.
谢了  鲍伯
Thanks, Bob.
刚才是什么情况
What just happened here?
我也没整明白
I'm not sure.
咱不能再开门了
We got to stop answering that door.
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
-你看见妈妈没  -没
- Have you seen Mom? - No.
很好
Good.
我现在看见了
I see her now.
嘿  老妈
Hey, Mom.
你穿这身是要去干啥
What's all this?
哦  我要去和杰克玩传球
Oh, um, I'm going to go play catch with Jake.
还要穿制服
In a uniform?
我们玩游戏也很认真的
We take catch pretty seriously.
你是在背着我打棒球么
Are you playing baseball behind my back?
不再是了
Not anymore.
为啥要这么对我
Why would you do that?
因为每回你看我打球
Because, Mom, every time you watch me play,
都会大喊大叫  完全失控的样子
you yell, you scream, and get totally out of control.
我不是那样的呀
That doesn't sound like me.
你就是那样的
Yes, it does.
我都不敢相信你在偷摸打球
I can't believe you're playing secret baseball.
只是对你保密而已  回见
It's only a secret to you. See ya.
查莉  宝贝
Charlie, honey, you'd
你肯定不会背着我干啥的对吧
never play a sport behind my back, would you?
-当然不会  妈咪  -真是我的好闺女
- No, Mommy. - That's my girl.
嘿  查莉  准备好垒球练习没
Hey, Charlie, you ready for T-ball practice?
嘿
Hey!
嘿  艾薇  有事啊
Hey, Ivy, what's up?
我爸刚买了辆新房车
So my dad, he just bought this new R.V.
你不介意去看一下
Would you mind checking it out,
然后大加赞赏一番吧
make a big deal about how cool it is?
那样他会很开心的
It would really make his day.
-小迪  -抱歉
- T? - Sorry.
我刚想起来
I was just remembering something
我爸说过不要开门的
my dad said about not answering the door.
欢迎登船  泰迪
Welcome aboard, Teddy.
我是船长兼飞行员哈利
I'm Captain Harry and the pilot of this vessel.
我猜你已经认识我的副驾驶了
I believe you know my copilot.
你好  泰迪
Ahoy, Teddy.
哇  温兹叔叔
Oh, wow, Mr. Wentz.
这简直太棒了
This is fantastic.
这就是可以移动的家啊
You know, it's a home that has a motor.
既可以用来休养生息
And it's recreational...
又可以当做交通工具
But it's also a vehicle.
厉害吧
And ain't she a beauty?
艾薇  带泰迪参观下吧
Ivy, give Teddy the tour.
好的
Sure.
好了
All right.
这是厨房  餐厅  客厅
This is the kitchen, dining room, living room...
你坐下试试座椅多舒适
You should check out how comfy the seats are.
好啊
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
好了  老爸  出发吧
Okay, dad. Let's go.
什么情况
What's going on?
还记得我们之前说的自驾游吧
Remember the road trip we wanted to take?
这就开始了哦
We're on it!
小子们  你们老爸即将成为婚礼主持
Okay, boys, your dad is about to become a wedding officiant.
我希望不要太复杂
Okay, I hope this isn't too complicated.
姓名
"Name".
邮箱地址
"Email address".
任命自己
"Ordain me".
-我去开门  -嘿
- I'll get it, dad. - Hey!
牧师鲍伯
Reverend Bob.
我们是来参加单身派对的
Hey, we're here for the bachelor party.
啥单身派对
What bachelor party?
你该举办的单身派对
The one you're throwing.
这是你作为伴郎的职责之一
You're my best man. It's part of the job.
那好  进来吧
Okay, well, come on in.
这是阿尼
This is Arnie.
我在邮局的同事
We work together at The Post Office.
你不是说有吃的么
I was told there would be food.
那好吧
Okay, well, uh...
你们先去楼下  我来组织
You guys go on downstairs and I'll put something together.
一起来啊  鲍伯
Hey, come on, Bob.
-我么  -是啊  四个人才能叫派对嘛
- Me? - Yeah. Four's a party.
三个人多凄凉
Three's just sad.
四个人也凄凉
Four can be sad, too.
你就不怕我家人不知道我去向而担心么
You ever think my parents might wonder where I am?
他们知道你去哪了
They know exactly where you are.
你妈都给你打包好行李了
Your Mom even packed your bag.
知道不  我要重新列清单
You know what? I'm making a new list,
你和我妈都会在上面
and you and my Mom are on it.
别纠结了  小迪  会很好玩的
Come on, T, it's gonna be fun.
我们这是去哪
Where are we going, anyway?
拉斯维加斯
Las Vegas.
哦  我喜欢维加斯
Oh, I love Vegas!
温兹叔叔  我们要多久才能到拉斯维加斯
Hey, Mr. Wentz, how long until we get to Las Vegas?
这个难说了
Oh, hard to say.
取决于我们在神秘车站逗留的时间长短
Depends on how much time we spend at the mystery stop.
还有神秘车站呢
We're making a mystery stop?
我喜欢哈利的神秘车站
Oh, I love Harry's mystery stops.
有时候它们比终点站还要有趣
Sometimes they're better than the final destination.
我好激动
Ooh, I just got tingly!
姑娘们激动不
Did you girls get tingly?
我们还是保持现状的好
We might as well get comfortable.
她要激动好一会的
She's gonna be tingly for a while.
嘿  老妈
Hey, Mom.
你好啊  加布里埃尔
Hello, Gabriel.
比赛打得如何啊
How was your baseball game?
很好  我们四比一赢了  我击中了两球
It was great. We won 4-1 and I had two hits.
听上去就是我们家长爱看的比赛啊
Huh, that sounds like something a parent might enjoy seeing.
老妈  你还要这样持续多久
Mom, how long is this gonna go on?
比赛季会持续多久
How long is baseball season?
听着  我承认
Look, okay, I admit that in the past,
过去我表现得有点
I may have gotten a little...
富有生气
Animated.
但人是会变的
But a person can change.
没错  人是会变的  那你呢
Yeah, sure, a person can change, but what about you?
如果你让我去看比赛
Look, if you let me go to your game I promise,
我保证会安静的  甚至让你察觉不到我在那儿
that I will be so quiet you won't even know that I'm there.
你觉得呢  托比  我能信她不
What do you think, Toby? Should I trust her?
不能
No.
别听他的  他才一岁
Don't listen to him. He's one.
但是没准他就是对的
And yet he's probably right.
那么
So...
我们来玩扑克
We've played Pinochle.
你们想怎么玩呢
Now what do you guys want to do?
那得你告诉我们了  伴郎
You tell us, best man.
他应该准备更多活动的
He should have planned more activities.
他失误了
He's dropping the ball.
知道不  你们老年人小声耳语
Just so you know, old guy
和我们年轻人正常说话效果是一样的
whispering is just like young guy talking.
你的伴郎态度不行
Your best man has a lot of tude.
我还是上楼再做些三明治吧
Well, I better get upstairs and make some more sandwiches.
要我帮忙么
Uh, you need some help with that?
不要  你自己再找别的借口吧
No, you come up with your own excuse.
你们俩
So you...
以前在邮局上班是吧
You guys were postal workers, huh?
我是除虫师
Exterminator.
他比他儿子还无趣
He's more boring than the son.
右车道结束
"Right lane ends".
小心落石
"Watch for falling rocks".
你在读路标么
Are you gonna read every road sign?
这是我旅途保持清醒头脑的方法
This is how I keep my sanity on these trips.
29B出口
"Exit 29B".
熊妈妈正带着熊宝宝们
This is Mama Bear cruising down the highway
在高速公路上行驶
with a couple of cubbies and
和宝贝老公一路向神秘车站驶去
a hubby-wubby on our way to a mystery stop.
马上回来
Come on back.
我是熊妈妈  有人在听么
This is Mama Bear. Anybody have their ears on?
看来都是木头人
Sounds like we got a mud duck.
肯定的了  宝贝老公
Affirmative to that, hubby-wubby.
这是行话  泰迪
That's C.B. Lingo, Teddy.
我说的是“他信号好像不好”
What I said was "Sounds like he's got a weak signal".
然后我的回答是“我也这么觉得  丈夫”
And I responded "I agree, husband".
限速  70
"Speed limit; 70".
你没偷看吧  没偷看吧  玛丽露
You're not peeking, now are you, Mary Lou?
哦没  我可不想毁了神秘车站的惊喜
Oh no! I wouldn't spoil a mystery stop.
好了
All right.
睁开你的眼睛
Open your eyes.
欢迎来到四角
Welcome to the four corners.
四角啥
Four corners of what?
艾薇  这是国内唯一一个
Ivy, this is the only place in the whole country
衔接四个州的地点
where four states connect at one single point.
亚利桑那  犹他  科罗拉多  还有新墨西哥
Arizona, Utah, Colorado, and New Mexico.
哦  哈利
Oh, Harry!
你又这样
Oh, you've done it again!
我知道
I know.
没有啥比这更刺激了
It doesn't get much more exciting than this.
艾薇  我能跟你说点事吗
Ivy, could I talk to you for a second?
行  你想在哪个州见我
Sure, which state would you like to see me in?
嘿  三明治咋还不来啊
Hey! How are the sandwiches coming?
再等一会儿
Couple more minutes.
嘿  达布斯夫人  你来这儿做什么
Hey, Mrs. Dobbs. What are you doing here?
-我有话必须跟你说  -出什么事了吗
- I have to talk to you. - Is everything okay?
PJ  有一个可怕的错误我需要忏悔
Oh, P.J., I have to confess a terrible secret.
你知道  我结过婚
You see, I was married before.
呃  那不算什么秘密
Well, that's not that much
因为大家都称你达布斯“夫人”
of a secret since your name is "Mrs. Dobbs".
-让我说完  -嗯
- Let me finish. - Mm hmm.
所有饭都是我第一任丈夫做的
My first husband did all the cooking,
所以我从来不知道如何做饭
so I never learned how.
但伯特一直说你手艺不错
But Bert raves about your cooking.
那是因为我总是私下里叫外卖
That's because I secretly order takeout,
然后弄得像我自己做的似的
and then serve it as if I made it myself.
嘿  我妈以前经常那么做
Oh, hey, my Mom used to do that...
当她还介意这事儿的时候
Back when she still cared.
我来这儿是因为知道你在上烹饪学校
I came over because I know you're going to cooking school
所以我希望你能教我点什么
and I was hoping you could teach me a few things.
好啊  我能给你上点课
Sure, I'd be glad to give you a few lessons.
我只是希望伯特不知道我来过这
I just hope Bert doesn't see me come over here.
嗯  如果他来了
Well, if he does...
你可以告诉他
You just tell him...
我在教你学踢踏舞
I'm teaching you how to tap dance.
好
Yeah.
让我想一下
I'll think of something.
笑一个  泰迪
Smile, Teddy!
温兹阿姨  你要拍我笑的话  或许你应该
Mrs. Wentz, if you want me to smile, you might want to,
站在我的前面  这样你才能看得到
stand in front of the part of me that smiles.
好了
Got it.
亚利桑那州的天气如何  玛丽露
Oh, how's the weather in Arizona, Mary Lou?
阳光明媚  并且  哦  哈利
Well, it's sunny and... oh, Harry!
上当了吧
Gotcha!
好吧  这真是
Well, this was...
咱们能走了吗
Can we get going now?
跟你走  艾薇
Right you are, Ivy.
接下来是最终目的地  拉斯维加斯  新墨西哥
Onto our final destination, Las Vegas, New Mexico.
嗯  你是说内华达吧
Um, you mean Nevada.
哦不不不  那个拉斯维加斯都去腻了
Oh, no, no, no, no. That Las Vegas has been done to death.
我们要去新墨西哥的拉斯维加斯
We're going to Las Vegas, New Mexico.
新墨西哥也有拉斯维加斯吗
There's a Las Vegas, New Mexico?
历史悠久
The original.
我以为我们要去
Uh, I thought we were going to
那个有SPA  泳池  还有商场的拉斯维加斯
the one with the spas, the pools and the shopping.
新墨西哥的拉斯维加斯有什么
What's in Las Vegas, New Mexico?
驯马人博物馆
The rough-rider museum.
世界上最大的仙人掌
The world's largest cactus.
艾薇  你知道这些吗
Ivy, did you know about this?
我不记得了
I don't recall.
真的
Really?
那么我来告诉你我记得啥
Because I'll tell you what I recall.
第一  你想出来这个自驾游的主意
First, you came up with the idea for the road trip,
然后你诱惑我上了房车
then you lured me into the R.V.,
然后你顺便故意漏掉那个
and then you conveniently left out the crucial...
拉斯维加斯的关键词“新墨西哥”
"New Mexico" Part about Las Vegas, New Mexico.
艾薇  你没跟泰迪说我们要去新墨西哥
Ivy, you didn't tell Teddy we were going to New Mexico?
她都没说我们会把车开出车道
She didn't tell me we were leaving the driveway.
哈利  要是泰迪不想
Harry, if Teddy doesn't
来这次旅行  那么我们应该启航返程
want to be on this trip, we should go home.
什么  看不了驯马人
What?! No Rough Riders?
没有大仙人掌
No big cactus?
我们可以下次来
We can come back another time.
来吧  亲爱的
Come on, honey.
老爸  你在做什么
Dad, what are you doing?
试一下心破碎在四大州的感觉
Seeing what it feels like to have my heart broken in four states.
你做这个干啥
Why you doing that?
因为满垒  盖比准备好击球
Because bases are loaded, and Gabe is up to bat,
并且我说好了会保持冷静
and I promised I'd stay calm.
-一好球  -什么
- Strike one! - What?!
你是不是
Are you out of your ...
忘了你家的邮编
Zip code?
假如你忘了的话  邻居会帮你的
Because if you are, welcome to the neighborhood.
二好球
Strike two!
裁判员  你真臭
You stink, ump.
啥  那是查莉说的
What? It was Charlie.
我以为你不会告诉你妈比赛的事
I thought you weren't gonna tell your Mom you were playing.
是啊  我尽我最大努力了
Yeah, I gave it my best shot.
三振出局
Strike three!
啥  你开玩笑吧
What?! Are you kidding me?!
哪个星球的规则告诉你这算出局
On what planet is that considered a strike?
你是我见过最不会找借口的裁判员
You are the sorriest excuse for an ump I've ever seen!
你以为你能做的更好
You think you can do better?
-对  -好
- Yeah. - Fine.
我以为你变了
I thought you changed.
我是变了
I did...
然后我又变回来了
Then I changed back.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么  这
Now this...
就是我们所说的勺子
Is what we call a spoon.
跟我念  勺子
Say it with me now, "Spoon".
我们能加点速不  婚礼就在明天
Can we speed this up? The wedding's tomorrow.
嘿  发生什么事了
Hey, what's going on here?
五  六  七  八
A five, six, seven, eight.
我是来给伴郎拿戒指的
I came over to give my best man the rings,
但看上去这儿有点不对劲
but it seems like there's something going on here.
伯特  有些事我必须跟你坦白
Bert, there's something I have to confess.
我
I...
我不会做饭
I can't cook.
一直以来你都在骗我
You've been lying to me all this time?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉没有用  婚礼取消了
Well, sorry's not good enough. The wedding's off.
这太糟糕了
This is awful.
我该怎么办
What am I going to do?
哦  我有个主意
Oh, I have an idea.
那是报时器  但我真有个主意
That was just the timer, but I do have an idea.
伯特  等等  等等  伯特
Bert, wait. Wait, Bert.
-你正在犯一个大错  -我心意定下来了
- You're making a huge mistake. - My mind's made up.
她骗我  这件事我无法原谅
She lied to me and I can't forgive that.
拜托  每个人都会犯错
Come on, everyone makes mistakes.
她说谎了吗  是的
Did she lie? Yes.
危机到信任了吗  是的
Did that hurt the trust? Yes.
我是不是不善于演讲  是的
Am I bad at these kinds of speeches? Yes.
但  但
But... but...
可是  伯特  那儿有个女人
But, Bert, there's a woman in
正为你而学着做饭
there who is learning how to cook just for you.
谁还会费这么大劲来讨你开心
Now who else is gonna go to that much trouble to make you happy?
这就是我想要的  伯特
That's all I ever wanted, Bert;
让你开心
To make you happy.
你真的啥菜也不会做
You can't cook anything?
我会热热狗
I can boil a hot dog.
那好吧  婚礼照常
Well, okay, the wedding's back on.
小迪
T...
对不起  我不该设计给你下套
I'm so sorry I tricked you.
我只是真心想让你过来
I just really wanted you to come along.
有你在身边一切就更有意思
Everything's more fun when you're around,
从幼儿园开始就这样子了
always has been ever since kindergarten.
我们是学前班才认识的
We met in preschool...
算了继续
But go on.
我只是想多花些时间和你在一起
I just wanted to spend some time with you.
我俩要去
We're both going away to
不同的大学  很快事情就会不同
different colleges soon and things are gonna change.
艾薇  我们会一直做好朋友的
Well, Ivy, we're always gonna be best friends.
我知道  但
I know, but...
还是不一样的
It won't be the same.
我会非常想念你
I'm gonna miss you so much.
我也会想你的  小迪
I'm gonna miss you too, T.
你要知道
And just so you know,
有你在身边我也觉得一切更有意思
everything's more fun when you're around too.
昨天的事是个例外  但大体上讲是不错的
This last day was a bad example, but generally speaking.
信不信由你  即使是这些事我也会想念的
Believe it or not, I'm even gonna miss them.
熊妈妈  这是泰迪熊  请回复
Mama Bear, this is Teddy Bear. Come on back.
这是熊妈妈  完毕
This is Mama Bear, over.
泰迪熊打算在整个去拉斯维加斯的问题上面
Teddy Bear would like to do a little flippity-flop
来个急转弯  完毕
on the whole Las Vegas thing, over.
泰迪熊  你说的是我正在想的吗
Teddy Bear, are you saying what I think you're saying?
我们要去拉斯维加斯  新墨西哥
We're going to Las Vegas, New Mexico!
收到
Copy that.
比赛开始
Play ball!
嘿  击球  击球  击球
Hey, batter, batter, batter!
嘿  击球  击球  击球  击球
Hey, batter, batter, batter, batter!
-嘿  -妈  妈  裁判不唠唠叨叨的
- Hey... - Mom, Mom, the umpire doesn't chatter.
抱歉  我就是喜欢那个环节
Sorry, I just really like that part.
一好球
Strike one!
嘿  你在看啥呢
Hey, what are you looking at?
我要让你麻利下场  快到晕头转向
I'll run you out of here so fast it'll make your head spin.
最起码你不用跟她回家
At least you don't have to go home with her.
不不不  太低了  下面
No, no, no, too low! Downstairs!
一坏球
Ball one!
你真臭  裁判
You stink, ump.
宝贝  不对不对  现在妈咪是裁判
Sweetheart, no, not now. Mommy's the ump.
我知道
I know.
嗯  查莉  我去了拉斯维加斯
Well, Charlie, I went to Las Vegas...
新墨西哥
New Mexico.
我来跟你说说这次旅行
And I'd tell you all about the trip,
但是正如他们说的  维加斯
but as they say, what happens in Vegas...
风平浪静
Is nothing.
但这无关紧要  因为是跟我最好的朋友在一起
But it doesn't matter because I was with my best friend,
那就表明我们玩的很开心
which means we had a lot of fun.
嘿  看这个
Oh, hey, check this out.
凭借“五分钟牧师”网站
So by the power vested
赋予我的授权
in me by the website "Five Minute Minister".
我宣布你们成为夫妻
I pronounce you husband and wife.
我老是受不了这种场面
I'm always a wreck at these things.
嗯  这个
Well, just a...
不过是邓肯家办的另一场婚礼
Just another Duncan-family
在起居室  给几乎不认识的人办的
living-room wedding between people we barely know.
祝他们好运   小查莉
Wish them good luck, Charlie.
你知道吗  整个婚礼事件让我有所深思
You know what? All this wedding stuff has really got me thinking.
咱们俩应该来个二度蜜月
You and I should go off on that second honeymoon.
你知道  就是我们一直讲的那个
You know, the one we're always talking about.
你是说巴黎
You mean Paris?
还能有哪儿
Where else?
你一定是在跟我开玩笑
You have got to be kidding me.
德克萨斯的巴黎
Paris, Texas?!
对啊
Oh, yeah.
你以为是哪个巴黎
What Paris we're you thinking of?
-在法国那个  -哦
- The one in France! - Oh!
那个都腻死了
That's been done to death.
这才是真正的好地方
This is where it's at.
拜托  谁会认为这地方比法国好
Oh, come on. Who's gonna choose this place over France?
你好  伙计们
Howdy, partners.
我们还不知道你们在周游世界呢
We didn't know that you were such world travelers.
嘿  你要想加入我们的话  我们下一站是雅典
Hey if you want to join us, our next stop is Athens.
-乔治亚州的  -还能有哪儿
- Georgia? - Where else?
希腊  让希腊情何以堪啊
Greece. Greece is where else.